(Raj:)How hot is it?
(Sheldon:)Uh, let's see.
704?
No, wait, it's on "clock."
No, the real answer
isn't much better.
(Sheldon:)102 degrees.
(Raj:)Well, that's what we wanted.
(Raj:)This is as hot
as the mines will be.
True.
(Sheldon:)Sheldon's Mine Simulation Log,
entry one.
(Sheldon:)Koothrappali's restating
of the obvious
(Sheldon:)is already getting on my nerves.
(Leonard:)Thanks again
for having us.
(Howard:)Oh, of course. What did
you guys want to talk about?
(Penny:)Well, you know, now
that we're engaged,
(Penny:)we had some questions about how
you handle money as a couple.
(Bernadette:)I told you they weren't gonna
ask us to swing with them.
(Howard:)I didn't think
they were going to.
(Howard:)I just wanted to have
a way to say no
(Howard:)without hurting
Leonard's feelings.
(Leonard:)Well... nailed it.
(Howard:)So what did you
want to know?
(Penny:)Well, do you guys ever
fight over money?